Contact

sheenteeah@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/cynthia-chunmsn-rn-cmsrn-89313463 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Public Speaking
PowerPoint
Microsoft Excel

Languages

English (Native or Bilingual) Korean (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

BLS- CPR Registered Nurse CMSRN

Honors-Awards

Elvira C. Larson Scholarship
Hassenplug Scholarship
Joy Jones Scholarship
Sister Jane Frances Scholarship
PRISM Award 2019-2022

Cynthia Chun, MSN, RN, CMSRN

Registered Nurse at St. Jude Medical Center Buena Park, California

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Event Planning, Microsoft Excel, Customer Service, Microsoft Word, and Strategic Planning. Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor of Science (B.S.) focused in Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse from UCLA and a Master of Science in Nursing (MSN) Leadership and Education from Vanguard University.

Experience

St. Jude Medical Center
Registered Nurse IV
February 2016 - Present (4 years 5 months)

- -Medical-Surgical/Telemetry Unit
- -Relief Clinical Coordinator
- -CDC Chair (2019 2020)
- -Education and Professional Development Chair (2020-2021)

Garden Grove Hospital Registered Nurse February 2015 - February 2016 (1 year 1 month)

-Telemetry Unit

GSCC

Registered Nurse June 2014 - January 2015 (8 months)

CLiCC

Consultant
September 2011 - July 2013 (1 year 11 months)

UCLA

Research Assistant April 2011 - June 2011 (3 months)

• Participated in data collection for a dissertation study regarding the elderly dealing with dementia and patient care

Education

Vanguard University of Southern California

Master's degree, Nursing Education and Leadership (2017 - 2019)

UCLA

Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse \cdot (2009 - 2013)